练习 4-2：Betty Bought a Bit of Better Butter。句子里的 T 都在弱读位置。
Exercise 4-2, Betty bought a bit of better butter. In the sentence, Betty bought a
这些 T 都听起来像轻柔的 D。
bit of better butter, all the t's are in weak positions, so they all sound like
慢慢逐词跟读这个句子。
soft d's. Repeat the sentence slowly, word by word. Betty bought a bit of better
感受舌尖轻触上齿后方的位置。
butter. Feel the tip of your tongue flick across that area behind your top teeth.
再说 Betty Bought a Bit of Better Butter 时，想象大提琴的音色。
Think of the music of a cello again when you say, Betty bought a bit of better
butter. Betty bought a bit of better butter. But, said she, this butter's
bitter. If I put it in my batter, it'll make my batter bitter. If you speak any
如果你会说西班牙语、日语、印地语、意大利语或荷兰语等语言，
language, such as Spanish, Japanese, Hindi, Italian, or Dutch, among others,
并且你的 R 会触碰牙齿后方，那么学习 American T 就很幸运。
where your R touches behind the teeth, you're in luck with the American T. Just
只要在脑中建立关联：当你看到中间位置的 T 时，
fix the association in your mind so that when you see a middle-position T, you
就自动用你母语里的 R 音。用你的母语口音说 Betty Bada Bida，
automatically give it your native R sound. Say, Betty Bada Bida with your native
但如果你是法国人、德国人或中国人就不要这样做。除了连读之外，American
accent, not if you are French, German, or Chinese. Along with liaisons, the American
T 也大大促成了英语顺滑、放松的声音。当你
tea contributes a great deal to the smooth, relaxed sound of English. When you
说 Adam 这样的词时，想象你刚看完牙医，嘴有点
say a word like Adam, imagine that you've been to the dentist and you're a little
麻；或者你喝了几杯，也可能你很困。
numb or that you've had a couple of drinks, or maybe that you're very sleepy.
你不会想费很多力气说 Atom，所以只要放松
You won't be wanting to use a lot of energy saying Atom, so just relax
然后说 Adam。男性名字 Adam 是非常顺滑流畅的音。
everything and say Adam. The masculine name Adam. It's a very smooth fluid sound.
与其说 Betty bought a bit of better butter，那样身体上更费力，
Rather than saying Betty bought a bit of better butter, which is physically more
不如试试放松地说 Betty bought a bit of better butter。这样很容易，因为你
demanding, try Betty bought a bit of better butter. It's easy because you
真的不需要太多肌肉紧张。阶梯概念
really don't need much muscle tension to say it this way. The staircase concept
会帮助你理清各种 T 音。如果你
will help clarify the various T sounds. The American T can be a little tricky if
根据拼写来发音，American T 可能会有点难。
you base your pronunciation on spelling.